<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string name="add_values">Add values to the chart</string>
    <string name="x">X</string>
    <string name="y">Y</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="new_series">New series</string>


    <string name="com.twitter.sdk.android.CONSUMER_KEY">gcnlJpaaYVHVT1UQ9CcIUGDpW</string>
    <string name="com.twitter.sdk.android.CONSUMER_SECRET">UCcCrJAFAOyTPKJinvs5NShwgkvVFpjOZromPNYOiuBGHjJOWk</string>


    <string name="app_name">Mandolapp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nav">NavActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Menu</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Menu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_drawer">Menu</string>
    <string-array name="planets_array">
        <item>Report</item>
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Statistics</item>
        <item>Saved Reports</item>
        <item>Report History</item>
        <item>Help</item>
        <item>Settings</item>


    </string-array>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_websearch">Web search</string>
    <string name="app_not_available">Sorry, there\'s no web browser available</string>
    <string name="intro_message">Hello World</string>
    <string name="navigationdraweractivity_title">Navigation Drawer Example</string>
    <string name="navigationdraweractivity_description">This example illustrates a common usage of the DrawerLayout widget in the Android
            support library.</string>

    <string-array name="category_array">
        <item>Religious</item>
        <item>Gender</item>
        <item>Sexual</item>
        <item>Class</item>
        <item>Politics</item>
        <item>Ethnicity</item>
        <item>Nationality</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="authority_array">
        <item>Authority 1</item>
        <item>Authority 2</item>
        <item>Authority 3</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="search_app_array">
        <item>Twitter</item>
        <item>Facebook</item>
        <item>Browser</item>
        <item>Picture</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="search_field_array">
        <item>Date</item>
        <item>Description</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="select_string">Select an item</string>

    <string name="intro_slide1">
        Welcome to Mandolapp. The application designed by the University of Cyprus to help the
        fight against online hate speech. Swipe left to begin your intro tutorial.
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide2">
        Hate speech is public expressions which spread, incite, promote or justify hatred,
        discrimination or hostility towards a specific group. They contribute to a general climate
        of intolerance which in turn makes attacks more probable against those given groups. - ILGA Europe
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide3">
        Using Mandolapp you can report images from your library, as well as Twitter content and public
        Facebook posts from their respective application. You can also report any other content you may encounter using an internet browser such as posts
        or comments that may in your opinion be related to hate speech, provided they have a link.
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide4">
        To begin, open Mandolapp and press the Start Mandolapp Bubble button. A bubble will appear telling you
        what you can do next.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide5">
        To report a picture from your library, press the button provided and press on a picture from your
        library.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide5_1">
        Next, choose a category for the report and the authorities you wish to send it to. More
        details about the authorities can be found in the help section. You can also choose to give
        your report an optional description.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide6">
        To report a post open the corresponding app(Twitter, Facebook, or an Internet Browser). The bubble will know which app you just opened and
        tell you what to do next.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide6_1">
        Copy the link of a post by following the instructions of the bubble.
        Then, the bubble will notify you that it has the link of the post. Choose a category, an authority and optionally give a description. You
        can also choose to save the report for later, without having to choose a category or an authority at that moment.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide7">
        If you want to get rid of the bubble you can get it back at any moment by pressing on the Mandolapp
        notification without having to visit the main app again. You can completely get rid of the notification
        by pressing the Stop Mandolapp button from the main app.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="intro_slide8">
        You can also navigate to different sections of the app using the slide in menu on the left.
        More helpful and detailed information can be found in the help section.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
    </string>


    <string name="about">
        Mandolapp is an application designed and developed by the University of Cyprus to help in
        the fight against online hate speech. This application was developed under the Mandola
        project. Mandola is a project which runs from 2014 to 2020 and is funded by the Rights, Equality
        and Citizenship (REC) Programme of the EU Commission.\n The Mandolapp application is designed to
        give you the ability to anonymously report hate speech content you come across while on the internet, while
        striving to provide you a very smooth and convenient user experience.
    </string>

    <string-array name="category_explanation">
        <item>Religious:\nContent that may present hate speech towards a person’s religion.</item>
        <item>Gender:\nContent that may present hate speech towards a gender (e.g. women).</item>
        <item>Sexual:\nContent that may present hate speech towards a person’s sexual orientation, sexual harassment or sexual content that is inappropriate.</item>
        <item>Class:\n
        Content that may present inter-class or inter-school hate speech between students or other members of the school community.</item>
        <item>Politics:\nContent that may present hate speech towards politicians or political ideas.</item>
        <item>Ethnicity:\nContent that may present hate speech towards an ethnic group (e.g. black people).</item>
        <item>Nationality:\nContent that may present hate speech towards people from a different nation.</item>
        <item>Other:\nContent that doesn’t belong in any other category</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="authority_explanation">
        <item>Authority 1:\nAuthority 1 explanation</item>
        <item>Authority 2:\nAuthority 2 explanation</item>
        <item>Authority 3:\nAuthority 3 explanation</item>


    </string-array>

    <string name="TwitterInstructions">
        Using Mandolapp you have the ability to report tweets from the Twitter application.
        You may report any tweet that contains hate speech according to your judgment, even comments
        of tweets, since every comment is a tweet of itself.\n\n\n

        Step 1:\n
        Launch Mandolapp bubble
        \n\n
        Step 2:\n
        Open Twitter Application. The bubble will recognize it and provide you with details on what to do next
        \n\n
        Step 3:\n
        Find a tweet you want to report. Press on the arrow on the upper right corner of each tweet. From
        the menu that will appear press Copy Link to Tweet
        \n\n
        Step 4:\n
        Mandolapp will recognize that you copy the link and provide you with a message. Once you open
        the bubble you will see the tweet loaded and a form to report.
        \n\n
        Step 5:\n
        You have to choose at least one category that the hate speech belongs to and an authority to send
        the report. More details for this can be found in the help section. Optionally, you can choose
        to give a description for the report as well. Once the form is completed, report by simply pressing
        the Report Now button. If you don\'t want to report at that moment you can choose to save the report
        to be reported later, without having to complete the form at the time of saving.
        \n

    </string>

    <string name="FacebookInstructions">
        Using Mandolapp you have the ability to report posts from the Facebook application.
        You may report any post that contains hate speech according to your judgment. Please note however
        that in order to report a facebook post it must be public, meaning that it must be a post
        the can be seen by everyone and not just be the friends of the person that posted it.\n\n\n

        Step 1:\n
        Launch Mandolapp bubble
        \n\n
        Step 2:\n
        Open Facebook Application. The bubble will recognize it and provide you with details on what to do next
        \n\n
        Step 3:\n
        Find a post you want to report. Press on the three vertical dots on the upper right corner of each post. From
        the menu that will appear press Copy Link
        \n\n
        Step 4:\n
        Mandolapp will recognize that you copied the link and provide you with a message. Once you open
        the bubble you will see the post loaded and a form that must be completed in order to report.
        \n\n
        Step 5:\n
        You have to choose at least one category that the hate speech belongs to and an authority to send
        the report. More details for this can be found in the help section. Optionally, you can choose
        to give a description for the report as well. Once the form is completed, report by simply pressing
        the Report Now button. If you don\'t want to report at that moment you can choose to save the report
        to be reported later, without having to complete the form at the time of saving.
        \n

    </string>

    <string name="BrowserInstructions">
        Using Mandolapp you can report any public content that you may encounter using an internet browser, by copying
        its link. Therefore in order to report something it must have a public link that is available to you.
        Such content may range from post or comments on social media or news sites accessed on an internet
        browser, to whole webpages.\n\n

        Step 1:\n
        Open an Internet browser application. The bubble will recognize it and provide you with details on what to do next\n
        Step 2:\n
        Copy the link of the content you wish to report\n
        Step 3:\n
        Mandolapp will recognize that you copy the link and provide you with a message. Once you open
        the bubble you will see the content loaded and a form that must be completed in order to report.\n
        Step 4:\n
        You have to choose at least one category that the hate speech belongs to and an authority to send
        the report. More details for this can be found in the help section. Optionally, you can choose
        to give a description for the report as well. Once the form is completed, report by simply pressing
        the Report Now button. If you don\'t want to report at that moment you can choose to save the report
        to be reported later, without having to complete the form at the time of saving.
        \n

    </string>

    <string name="PictureReport">
        Using Mandolapp you can report pictures from your library.

        Step 1:\n
        Press the button with the camera icon on the main screen of the bubble\n
        Step 2:\n
        You will be redirected to your pictures library. Once there choose a picture by clicking on it.\n
        Step 3:\n
        The bubble will open and you will see the selected picture and a form that must be completed in order to report.\n
        Step 4:\n
        You have to choose at least one category that the hate speech belongs to and an authority to send
        the report to. More details for the categories and authorities can be found in the help section. Optionally, you can choose
        to give a description for the report as well. Once the form is completed, report by simply pressing
        the Report Now button.
        \n
    </string>

    <string-array name="FAQ_array">
        <item>What is Hate Speech?:\n\nWhile there is no universal comprehensive legal definition of hate speech, it is useful to
            consider and reflect on the views of the Committee of Ministers of the Council of Europe
            which has stated, that they consider that “hate speech shall be understood as covering
            all forms of expression which spread, incite, promote or justify racial hatred,
            xenophobia, anti-Semitism or other forms of hatred based on intolerance, including:
            intolerance expressed by aggressive nationalism and ethnocentrism, discrimination and
            hostility against minorities, migrants and people of immigrant origin”. </item>
        <item>Is the reporting process really anonymous?:\n\nYes. No information is sent to the authorities about you.</item>
        <item>What happens after I send a report?:\n\nThe authority you choose to send the report to is solely responsible for the
        handling of the reports.</item>
        <item>Why does the application ask for the Usage Access Permission at the beginning?:\n\n
            The application aims at providing you the best possible user experience. The only reason we ask for that permission
            is so the application can understand that you launched Twitter, Facebook, or Internet browser application. That way the application
            will catch content you copy only inside those applications and it will be able to give you specific details for each
            application you might open. The application DOES NOT use any other information about the usage of your phone
            or your application whatsoever.
        </item>
        <item>Can the report be in languages other than english?:\n\n
        Yes you can report posts in any language. However, keep in mind that the authority you send the report to might not
        support or understand you language</item>
        <item>How do I know what category of Hate Speech refers to?:\n\n
        You can find more details about what each category of Hate Speech refers to in the help section</item>
        <item>How do I know who each authority is?:\n\n
        You can find more details about each authority in the help section</item>
        <item>There is a notification on my phone that won\'t go away. What do I do?\n\n
        In order to provide you the best possible user experience the notification is always open so that when
        you discard the application bubble you can relaunch it from anywhere simply by pressing on the notification.
        If you want to stop the notification along with the application just press the STOP MANDOLAPP button from
        the main screen of the main application. If you want to be able to use the application without the notification
        you must choose to disable notifications from the Mandolapp application in your settings.</item>
        <item>The application doesn\'t work properly. What do I do?:\n\n
        If you think that something doesn\'t work as expected you can always press the STOP MANDOLAPP button from
        the main screen of the main application and then start the bubble again.</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>
